"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
(Hua Yunzhuang Hotel)
(Alarm clock July 5, Sunday, 7 a.m.)
white agent
- get up
- What's wrong?
Get up quickly
Oops
Oh my god
Put on this one instead
Huh? OK
Oh my god
"Our company's VDSL broadband speed..."
"Our company's VDSL..."
"...average download speed is 46Mbps
The upload speed is 10Mbps”
"ACT has a much lower number of fault declarations..."
This car is so slow
It's quite slow
How can we do business when the car is so slow?
Would you like to try again?
"With the others..."
"Compared to other companies
ACT has a much lower number of fault claims”
- Luo Su
- Huh?
Do I look like Leslie Cheung?
Ah
Sorry, I almost cursed
"Compared to other companies
ACT has a much lower number of fault claims”
That’s right! That’s it!
- Thank you!
- You're welcome
thank you
ACT please come in
- Yes!
- Hello!
Thank you for your hard work. I will send you the contract later.
- Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Nalai Communication Please come in
Sauna? Or have a drink?
Let’s take a sauna first
-Sauna!
- I'm exhausted
(Missed call, Executive Director Bai Zhengtai)
Hello, can we meet?
You sound so depressed on the phone
It tastes quite delicious now
That’s weird
I clearly have no appetite at home.
But as soon as I see you, my appetite suddenly comes over
So weird
- So what are you going to do?
- What to do?
The issue of the riser tube was ruined.
Do you still plan to stay with the company?
You guy, who said you were in trouble?
After getting into such a big trouble, it’s basically finished.
Aren't you listening to me? I've solved it all
You cause trouble yourself and deal with the consequences yourself.
What's there to show off?
You are back to the starting point
I told you it can be undone.
Do you really think you still have time to redeem yourself?
Brother Zhengtai
Will never betray me
He can't betray me
Your master who became the standing master?
Ouch, Minister Kim
The senior executives will stand with the company
You're not in a gang
What about loyalty and betrayal?
What do you know?
A guy who hangs out in slippers during the workday
You know nothing about big business
In that case, why did you call me?
I don't know who else to turn to except you
- drink
- Cheers
- Hello, gentlemen.
- Hi
Sorry for interrupting your chat.
We would like to introduce to you two
A very nice commercial building
- give
- thank you
If you invest now
You can collect six to seven million won in monthly rent in the future
The project is located in the third phase of the new city and is still under construction.
held by our company
Some stores are selling at special prices
Not much left
Our special offer shop
Price is lower than market price
OK we will consider it
OK
It will be completed in two or three months
So you have to act quickly
- OK
- thank you
- Goodbye
- I...
(The monthly salary will be cut off and the monthly rent will not be)
What are you doing? Show me
Kim Nak-soo, listen to me carefully
If you want to survive the remaining fifty years,
First you have to tear it off
- This kind of leaflet
- Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Second, drink three cans of beer
Food to go with drinks should not exceed 1,500 won
Hey, you have a building
If you charge 30 million a month in rent, you should also spend some money.
Only in this way can the real economy function normally
That's how I have the money to buy a house, idiot
Oh my god
People nowadays are so generous with their money.
All installed
- thank you bye
- thank you
Mother-in-law, this is the latest model that can be connected to a mobile phone
Quite...expensive
quite expensive
Are they just showing off in front of me on purpose?
Thank you so much
Mom, this is much better than what we have at home.
This is a high-end model that was just released last month
Sister
- past point
- Hey!
Sister, have you asked him?
What to ask?
Have you asked your brother-in-law about Xiangzhe Company?
No
We treat you to such an expensive hotel meal
What have you been doing during this time?
I'm very busy
What are you busy with? You don’t have a job
What about you?
What else do you do besides that enzyme group purchase?
I'm preparing for the exam
What certificate?
pet mortician
Isn't it great?
It does sound promising.
Right?
I have been preparing for a while before
Real estate agent exam coming up
Sang Cheol! Mom!
My sister is going to take the real estate agent qualification certificate test
Hey, what's so funny?
- Is that your brain?
- Ouch
You are fifty years old
Haven’t you realized that you are not meant for reading?
- Mom!
- Really
She's so funny
Sister, that's the national qualification certificate
Did you know?
She must have thought it was similar to a driver's license
unbelievable
Try it. You can definitely do it.
Right!
I bought a top-of-the-line SUV and it will arrive in two months
If you pass the exam
I'll give you that car
- I'm serious
- Wife
What if she really passes the exam?
I'm not saying I don't want to give it to you
As soon as the car arrives
I didn't even remove the protective film and sent it to you as is.
I'm serious
Wife, stop talking
What's wrong?
Sister has already passed the driver's license exam, I'm sure she can do it this time too
You can do it, sister. You will definitely pass.
Episode 4: Life hanging by a thread
Were you busy before?
Yes bro
I took a nap for too long.
That's right
What's the matter?
Well, nothing's wrong
Let’s have dinner together sometime
Of course that's good
Are you free next week?
Well...
How about tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Isn’t it convenient on Monday night?
Well I...
How about Tuesday?
Brother
How about you come to my house next weekend?
Your home?
say to my wife
She hasn't seen you for a long time. I hope you can come.
Oops, go home...
It would be too much trouble for you to go home
It's okay
Then come to my house next week
next sunday night
Minister Kim, we'll do it after work
Let’s eat something near the company
No, I want to treat you well
next sunday night
Just come to my house, okay?
Really
It’s settled. Goodbye
There's really nothing we can do about this guy
Not right now. I have to buy some time.
What time are you trying to gain? What happened?
- He Zhen
- Huh?
Please help your husband this time
If you need help while cooking, hire one
I will help too
Have you encountered any difficulties recently?
No, no difficulty
I just invited Executive Bai to come home
Just to keep in touch with each other
Husband
It's okay, trust me
It's okay
Husband, speaking of Sang Cheol...
Xiang Zhe?
What happened to him?
The last time I saw that YouTuber
Didn't he say anything?
No What does it mean?
Wait
How do you know this?
Can't I know?
So what do you want to say?
Sang Cheol will start his own company soon
What then?
In what financial technology field does he want to show his talents?
So?
Just in case
If you can't be promoted to a senior executive this year
Do you have other plans?
you want me to
If you can't be promoted to a senior executive, why don't you work for Sang-cheol?
He promised that the treatment would be much better than now.
What on earth did you say about me behind my back?
I didn't say anything
you must have said something
Otherwise, why would Xiangzhe let me work for him?
I'm just asking what you think
Give me better treatment?
Did you take my salary or something?
Have you told your sister's family everything?
No, that was what Xiangzhe found out about himself.
That guy thought money was everything
He's just an ignorant technician
he thought
Do you work in Silicon Valley yourself?
How dare he?
- Husband
- Really
Whether it’s family or not
Can you at least consider it?
It’s not like he asked you to clean the building
He will treat you like a seasoned professional
Experienced professional?
Do you think it’s me he wants?
Otherwise what is it?
This is it, okay?
The connections held by the ministers of large companies
Don't be stupid
If I really go, he will drain my connections.
Kick me out again
Do you think he won't do this?
Even if I can't get promoted
I would never work for him either.
I made it very clear. Go tell him.
Don't go around talking useless nonsense all day long
Okay, whatever you want
What about you?
Do you think you are a top talent?
Really
Do you think the sales director of a large Korean company
Are you the only one?
- Stop talking
- If you are really that powerful
Why did you accept Sang-cheol's help then?
You should have been like that just now
Lose your temper and say: "I can handle everything myself"
That's different
He was the one who called first and asked for help.
Do you know why he called you?
...ACT sales team actually sent me an email
Ask me to take down the video
Why should I remove it?
Why? Why exactly?
brother-in-law
You said you were familiar with him, right?
Well, we know each other, right?
Then can you
Help my husband get in touch
Allow him to talk to the other party in person?
Did you ask him for help?
Yeah, I'm thinking
You have enough trouble in the company
That's why I'm helping you
Does this also hurt your self-esteem?
Hello Kim Nak Soo
Oh my god
Do you know what your biggest problem is?
You don't know how to be grateful
You always thought you got where you are today on your own
- enough
- You also have a bad personality
Overly sensitive, bad tempered
You're such a terrible person, Kim Nak-soo.
you went too far
On Sunday, whether it's Executive Bai or the president himself,
I won't do anything
Wife
Whether you want to braise pork ribs or make hand-made noodles
Do it yourself
Wife, you just promised to help me
When did I say that?
I've done enough
I pulled Soo-gyeom up
I have also done my duty to my husband’s family.
And try your best to maintain your self-esteem
Wife
Our married life...
Now onto the next chapter
What are you talking about?
Got it?
Ouch, you scared me. What are you doing?
Wife!
(ACT Building 1, ACT Building 2)
- Minister Kim...
- Isn’t Minister Kim here yet?
He is rarely late
You're here, Minister Kim.
So heavy
What is all this, Minister?
This is for you Song Hee
And Narihisa
- give
- Wait
Why are you all so surprised?
To Mr. Song
thank you minister
Are you...
Saving points?
What does it mean?
Nothing. Thank you, Minister.
OK...
- Minister Kim
- Huh?
Are you...
- Are you going to resign?
- What are you talking about?
Is it weird for me to buy you a cup of coffee?
- Not surprising
- Thank you Minister
- drink
- thank you
Let's go to the rooftop and talk.
- OK
- I'll put this down first.
Let's go out and run some business
Now?
Let’s just call this week “Special Sales Week”
It’s been a while since I’ve been on the front line
Let's try our best to have a big fight
Minister, I still have a lot of work to do.
I can't go out to work now
you...
Do you really have that much work?
Last time you asked us
Come up with five ideas for new products
You can take your time with that one
Minister, shall we go have a cigarette?
I didn't bring cigarettes
I brought it
- Don't talk about me behind my back.
- Come on
You can definitely tell they weren't too happy.
Why is everyone so harsh on me?
What did I do wrong?
It's just like politics
If the support rate is not high, nothing can be accomplished.
I'm on your side
But if you ask me to put down what I'm doing and go run the business
That's not easy either
So what should I do?
You need populism now
Not enough coffee and donuts?
Of course not enough, Minister.
We're not new recruits waiting for church to hand out snacks.
ok
Please help me, everyone.
As long as you help me
I will definitely reward you with an excellent performance review
Future Agent Kwon, Section Chief Zheng, and Deputy Chief Song
I promise you will get what you want during your performance review
Get ready for a promotion!
- OK!
- Make achievements!
- Get promoted together!
Do it again!
- Make achievements!
- Get promoted together!
I want to be a class principal!
That Section Chief Song acted alone
Chengjiu, come with me
- OK
- Yes Minister
Songxi is arranging the route. Let's leave quickly.
- OK
- Do you still have a car?
We didn't apply in advance, so there's only one car left.
Then hurry up and apply. Don't let that car be snatched away.
- I'll drive my own car
- OK
I'm looking for a car
- You go get the key.
- OK
Hey wait!
You have to tell me the license plate number
Good 7982
I'm leaving first
OK, be careful on the road
Good 7982
Where is 7982?
Where is it?
wow
(Seoul 32 DA7982)
Minister Kim
Judging from the key, the car must be very old.
Did you find it?
here
Where?
This car
Damn it
Oh my god
- wow
- Can the car still move?
open the door
Good
wow
The kilometers are less than I thought.
Only 280,000?
This car is too big for running business
So we rarely open
Still a manual transmission?
Why don't they get rid of this car?
Shall I drive it?
What?
I'll do it
Oh my god, the car can still run.
I feel like this might be a good sign
Executive Bai
Hi
Hello
Where has everyone gone?
They went on a field trip
All three people went?
Yes
(Minister Kim Nak-soo)
When can they come back?
Well...let me ask
No, it's okay
good
- Then keep working.
- OK
Let me see
Organize high-quality renewal customers into tables...
(Contracted company)
...sent to Section Chief Song
(Route B, Section Chief Song)
Companies unlikely to renew...
(Route A: Minister Kim and Agent Jung)
...just send it to Minister Kim
He is the minister after all
(Sales group chat)
(Send files)
Have you received the document from Songxi?
Yes I received it
We are going to start from Namyangju and go around in a clockwise direction
You start from Bucheon and go through that area
Yes Minister
Thank you for your hard work
See you tomorrow, Minister
- OK
- all the best
Good
Wow, I drove this car for a few years when I was an agent.
I haven’t opened it once since then.
Really?
This car is the same age as my son Soo-gyeom
Isn’t it interesting?
Soo Gyeom is already in college
You look happy, Minister
I haven’t felt so motivated at work in a long time.
Let's go
Let’s go!
When drinking with superiors
Turn your head and drink
This is polite in Korea
Isn't that disrespectful?
Doesn't that mean you are ignoring the other person?
No
- This is a cultural difference
- What?
If you drink face to face
It means both parties have equal status
But we think this is rude to our elders
So
We have to lower our heads or turn our heads to drink
- Is that so?
- Right
Have you decided yet?
Let me help you break out of your shell
Just like a bird breaking out of its shell, I will break it
The shell of this company
So that you can spread your wings and fly high
(CDO Kim Soo-gyeom)
welcome to the jungle
Welcome to join brother
(CDO Chief Disruption Officer Kim Soo-gyeom)
Don't you think you've been thinking about it for too long?
I'm not that casual person
Your eyebrows are still the same as when you were a child
What?
You brought this too
(ID card Kim Soo-gyeom)
Yes
Looking forward to your performance
my chief saboteur
Let's work
(KEPCO KKE)
I'm afraid this won't work
We have cut our budget this year by 30%
If you choose our low-cost maintenance package
You don't need to replace any equipment
Look here
For a one-year contract, it only costs 890,000 won per month.
You only need to pay an extra 150,000 won per month
We can equip you with a dedicated security team
This means we can respond in real time
As soon as an external hacker attack occurs
We can block it immediately
It can be said to be an iron wall!
(energy drink)
We will bear the entire cost of server replacement
In addition, we will give you another 7% discount
Wait, Minister?
You are public officials serving your country.
As a token of our gratitude, we offer a special offer
go out
I get angry when I hear ACT
I promise to take care of the maintenance myself
- Minister, let's go.
- Report for repairs in the middle of the night, I will be on call
- Also on holidays
- let's go
- Really on call
- Let's take our leave now.
- Same for Christmas Eve
- What a waste of maintenance
- Please...
Don't let me see you again!
(Korea Telecom Development)
- This...
- Sorry
Hello everyone, I’m from ACT.
Are you here to discuss contract renewal?
- Right
- Sign it
Then...
good
- Give me one to eat
- thank you
- OK
- Are you ready?
(service area)
Minister Kim
- thank you
- give
Ouch
So comfortable
This is the first time I visit 20 customers in one day
That's less than half
Songxi seems to have given us the harder route
Songxi is really...
It's time for us to go back
- Chengjiu
- Huh?
Shall we stay nearby tonight?
What?
If I go back to Seoul, I'll come back tomorrow
It must be tiring going back and forth
Forget it, it's not the past anymore.
let's go
That's a great idea, Minister Kim.
Huh?
I'll drive this time
Get in the car, Minister.
- Are you sure?
- You must be tired.
(Bisheng Real Estate Examination Academy)
- I just told you
- Do you want to cancel the refund?
Do you want to re-register?
Yes
But the course has already started
I will study hard and try to catch up.
OK, please wait a moment
Team leader, we have a tricky situation now.
(2024 Hall of Honor
The student who passed the exam fastest)
Can she join the class midway?
I know it's not possible in principle
But do you think you can be accommodating?
good
- Who?
- Don't know
(entrance door)
Sister, do you want to come to our house?
No
Hello
Write a letter of guarantee!
Guarantee?
When will your car arrive?
Why do you ask?
If I passed the exam
You'd better give me the car as you said before!
Write a letter of guarantee!
Sorry
Sister...
Sister
Did what I said irritate you that much?
You said I would never fail the exam!
Of course you can't pass the exam
Just rely on your brain
That's good
Then let’s write it down in black and white
Don't be shy then
Sister
Haying, that's my eighth wedding anniversary gift to you...
OK! Just write.
Wife!
But sister
That car is top-of-the-line, costing almost 90 million won.
If you don't pass the exam, what are you going to give me?
What?
Think about it
Is this bet too unfair?
You have to bet something, right?
What do you want me to bet on too?
Forget it
You don't have to stake anything
If you pass the test, my car will be yours.
If you haven't passed the exam...
Then you can just let me laugh at you for the rest of your life.
Ha Young
You really think of me as a joke, don’t you?
Of course
I know... you will never fail the exam
You'd better not regret it
No way
(Signed by Park Ha Young on May 12, 2025)
Sister
Wait...
(guarantee)
Minister Kim, would you like a beer?
OK
What should we eat to go with the wine?
What about the three-flavored squid? Really good
I'm back
Yeah
"The amount of tax paid in the supplementary declaration is the tax base multiplied by..."
("Real Estate Agents: Real Estate Law")
Mom, you have to take the exam again
Do you have a real estate agent qualification?
Yes
What about dad?
What happened to him?
I mean
I thought you would side with daddy
That was last week and now I'm different
I've been washing your dad's underwear for twenty years
It's time to do something for yourself now
Right?
- Right
- That's good
things you do with your friends
Is it going well?
Me?
Well...
- What are you doing?
- we can do it
- Come on
(22-day commemorative party)
it's your turn
What a pity
- It's okay
- Hey
- take your time
- Missed
- OK
Nice shot, Hannah.
- fast
- Hannah
- Come on
- fast
- OK
- Hannah
- Huh?
- I'm going home first
- Hannah, come on
- Come on, it's your turn
- It's your turn
- OK
- In!
- Yeah!
- You're in
- Awesome Hannah
- Goodbye
He's going to vote
beautiful
- Goodbye!
- Hurry up
quite difficult
It's hard, Mom
Isn't it?
Learning again after so many years
It's so difficult
Come on then
Good
I will work hard
(Motel)
So
Are you already living together?
Yes
Of course it's good
i love her
i care about her very much
I'm willing to do whatever she asks me to do
It's so fun to be with her
But...
i have been thinking
"Why doesn't she go back to her home?"
Naruhisa
Huh?
That's what marriage is like
I want to play games and clean the room
Take a break alone
But she just won't come home
Oh my god
but why i
Did you have this idea from the beginning?
This is your life from now on, Chengjiu
Minister Kim
Should I not get married?
The knot
- Why?
- Get married
Get married
Minister, are you asleep?
No
Can I ask you something?
Ask
This is how we run our business in a surprise manner
Can it really help you?
Or is this just
Did you do this because you thought it would be useful?
- Chengjiu
- Huh?
When life hangs on a thread in a baseball game
Just clear your mind
Thinking that there will always be a ball that I am good at hitting.
Then swing with all your might
This is the best tactic
What? Is it difficult to understand?
No I understand
But...
I probably won't be able to survive that time
Of course, Minister, you are different
Because you have a lot to protect
minister
I think what I'm really afraid of is not getting married
It’s the burden of being the head of the family
- Chengjiu
- Huh?
Imagine you are my age
Falling into the situation I am in now
get home from work
I found that all the lights at home were turned off and the living room was empty.
There's no smell of dinner in the kitchen
No one welcomes you home
at fifty
To bear that terrible loneliness...
Not everyone can do this
at least i can't
protect my family
Actually it is
Protecting myself
This is not a noble thing
I'm just protecting myself
You should record this saying...
fell asleep
(new recording)
Why are you recording something like this?
so ridiculous
Minister, we will meet in our dreams
When did he start recording?
good morning
Wow, so many
Haven't you read it all in the system?
See this with your own eyes
Only then did I realize how awesome you are
Got these renewals done in one day
You didn't give it to me on purpose
Is there a list of customers with high renewal rates?
Don’t hate Minister Kim so much
I don't hate him
They are two people together and...
The more you earn, the more responsibilities you have to take on
This is what a team leader should be like
- Hello Executive
- hello
- Hey
- Hello
Hi
Minister Kim went out again?
Oh no
He stayed near the client's company last night
Started working early this morning
That's it
He really works hard
Yes
- Then keep working.
- OK
work hard
- Goodbye
- Walk slowly every day
Goodbye
Why are you making people so uncomfortable, Nak Soo?
You mean when Naksu-senpai hit a hole-in-one?
A photo of you and two other sales department managers
Was it seen by people from the Korean Fair Trade Commission?
Really
This happened
Senior Nak Soo has been having a lot of bad luck lately.
It's really worrying
I did as you asked
good
I've listed the two combined groups...
(Sales team merge)
...expected effects and business division of labor
I also tried reassigning team members.
In the position of team leader...
(Team leader Du Zhenyu)
...you wrote your name
Yes
why are you so sure
Will you be the team leader instead of Kim Nak-soo?
Ah
Senior Luo Su this time...
Aren't we going to raise the pipe?
I think it's natural
You are really...
Never make things difficult for you
(Kukkiwon World Taekwondo Headquarters)
here conference room
(Small meeting room B)
(Korean national sport Taekwondo)
They are still having a meeting
good
You don't need to be too stressed, Minister Kim.
- Yeah, I know.
- After all, this is Taizheng Telecom’s territory.
Got the best
It’s no big deal if you didn’t grab it.
Yes
And we arrived just after the announcement came out
It's a bit late
they came out
Are you from ACT?
- Hello
- Nice to meet you
I am Minister Kim Nak-soo
I am agent Zheng Chengjiu
- OK
- Nice to meet you
Sorry, we just finished our meeting
Is it okay to start again in about 15 minutes?
Of course, no problem
Can we go in and wait?
Of course
Thank you for your hard work, Minister.
- Goodbye
Sorry, I'll be fine soon
It's okay. Take your time...
Section Chief Xu
give
Quit smoking?
Are you going to give one
Do people who almost died by burning charcoal offer cigarettes?
sorry
Forget it, I know you don't care about others.
I heard you resigned
But I didn’t expect you to go to Taizheng
You were a groom there? It was great.
What's the use
Salary is half of what it was in ACT
You guys are so cruel
Eat meat scraped from fly legs
Why don't you even miss this place?
Our situation is not good either.
you know
Our situation is many times worse
only here
Taizheng Telecom Talents
Avoid the big three telecom companies and take a breather
Can't you give up here?
As the deputy director of a small company
I ask you to hold your hand high
Minister of large companies
Minister Kim
It's time for us to go in
take care
please
How are you doing, Mr. Xu?
Not bad
What a coincidence to meet him here, right?
- Chengjiu
- Huh?
Let's not work too hard
Let's go after saying what needs to be said.
Of course
Do you remember what I just told you?
- Right
- OK
Based on the above advantages...
(a trustworthy partner)
...we want ACT to be
Kukkiwon’s most trustworthy partner
This concludes our introduction. Thank you.
thank you
Please turn on the light
- Please wait
- OK
Do you think this is okay?
Actually
We and our previous telecommunications provider Taizheng Telecom
Just finished the contract renewal meeting
Good
We have also seen the quotation you gave in advance
To be honest, judging from the price
It’s more cost-effective for us to renew the contract with Tai Zheng
We are not an online-focused company
And cooperate with Taizheng Telecom
It’s been almost ten years
We invite you to meet
I’m not trying to convince you to switch to our company right away.
But
Remember I just asked you to wait for 15 minutes?
remember
We have decided that starting from the second half of this year
All hosted events will be live streamed in 4K
Got it
Our existing data equipment and broadband network
It can’t support 4K live streaming at all
And waiting for Taizheng Telecom to build an OTT solution
It'll be a while yet
Yes, that's true
So can you now
Just issue a new quotation for us?
Of course
I will apply to the headquarters right away
I'll call a few more colleagues over
please wait
OK
thank you
Great, Minister
I really didn’t expect that I would have to report to Executive Bai
No, it's okay. I'll tell you later.
Good
That...Song Hee
Song Hee, we are at Kukkiwon
Can you help me with a quotation?
- Congratulations
Agent Li, a group just signed a contract with Kukkiwon
Did he really do it?
Well done, Minister Kim.
And I signed a super gigabit broadband package
Yes
Or the general contractor, even the construction was taken over.
Wait
(Quotation)
If 50 million per month, one year would be...
You don’t have to worry about this year’s performance indicators.
The minister can breathe a sigh of relief.
Yes
It seems that ginger is still spicy when old.
So awesome
- Congratulations
Nothing
(Executive Director)
Hello
I heard that a group just signed a big deal
Think about it from another perspective
If you were me, would you be able to laugh?
you say
I haven’t driven a manual transmission in a long time. This feels so good.
This seems to be the first time I've driven it since I was discharged from the army.
Minister Kim
When I used to drive for the division commander
That smooth shift...
Be quiet
good
Hey, forget it
Take a look, all the blood is soaked out
Very good
come on
Braised pork ribs...
(Prepare the sauce)
Sauce 8 tablespoons soy sauce
big spoon
(light soy sauce)
Soy sauce...
Stop!
What's wrong?
This is light soy sauce. You have to add dark soy sauce.
Is it different?
Yes
Really?
Give it to me Let me do it
good
- Stop!
- What's wrong?
You have to use a spoon, not a spoon
It says "big spoon"
- Oh my god
- Is this what you're using?
Ouch wait a minute
Hey Soo Kyum
Come and try some spinach
Why let him taste it? Taste it yourself
I don't know if the seasoning is suitable
Come and try
How is it?
Is it so unpalatable?
Wait
- get out of the way
- Oops
Why are you so strong?
- Oh my god
- I'll do it
Forget it, let me do it
I'll suck the floor
Stop it! What are you doing?
Oh my god
unbelievable
(Premium Korean beef gift box)
(Ballantine's 30 Years Old)
Forget it. What kind of whiskey are you drinking?
Just beer
- You can keep that one and drink it with your siblings.
- Coming
30 years?
- wow
- Too luxurious
We don't usually drink
- I'll do it
- Oops
pour on
- OK
- Ouch
- thank you
- So fragrant
Come on, have a drink too, wife
I asked him to drive before but he wouldn't drive.
Thanks to you I can finally have a taste
You should be nice to your siblings
Of course you don't know how good I am to her
thank you
Suqian, would you like a drink too?
Let me pour you a drink
OK, try it
Good
Come on, take the wine from the elders
Oh my god
This bottle of whiskey is older than you
That's right
come on
- Minister Kim
- Huh?
Would you like to make a toast?
- Me?
- Right
OK then
First...
my favorite
- My cute little deer
- Oops
-Dear Ms. Park Ha-jin
Because of you I can live
Ouch, you're so annoying. What's wrong with you?
And our Yonsei University students
Our pride and joy Soo Kyum
These two people are truly the reason for my existence.
- That's right
- Yes
and since I joined ACT
who has always given me a lot of guidance and help
Our Executive Director Bai Zhengtai
- Applause!
- I'm so...
Okay, that's enough
I'm serious for the past 25 years
I always consider you family
I feel closer than a real brother, you know?
Of course I know
- Right
- You and your brother are not very close.
Anyway, what I want to say is
we are a family
What is family?
Family is there no matter it rains or winds, love or hate
Whether it's noisy or laughing
People who will be together
Only those who can be together all the time are called family
So I suggest
I said "Let's fall in love"
How about you pick up "Never Leave, Never Give Up"?
- Okay, that sounds good.
- Then
Fall in love!
- Never give up!
Wait
Oops
Oh my god
started
Welcome to the world of angels
(May 22, 2003)
you are so beautiful
You were so young back then, right?
- How young
-Seriously
You look the same, sister-in-law.
Look! That’s you, Agent Bai, behind you
Please use warm applause
Welcoming friends and colleagues of the groom
Mr. Xu Taihuan
i love you
There is only you in my world
You are so excited!
I'm calling your name
Eat too much today
Right
- What's wrong?
- Soo Kyum
- Please don't do this.
- No
- Don't do this
- This isn't for you.
Don't let it be taken away. Keep it for yourself.
- Oops
thank you
Wait
I cooked a few dishes that my sister-in-law likes to eat, including fried matsutake mushrooms
There’s also soybean made from Korean beef tendons.
It tastes just right. She will definitely like it.
Take it back with you
You are so kind. Thank you, sister-in-law.
The driver will be here soon
No, tell the driver
Can you come back in 15 minutes?
I'm too full. Let's go for a walk.
Oh ok
Can you come back in 15 minutes?
Brothers and sisters, thank you for the hospitality. Let’s go back.
Okay, you come often
- I will
- OK
Suqian, go back with your mother
- Goodbye
- Let me get it
- Go inside
I'll take him to the car. Come back.
- Goodbye
- let's go
- OK
Ouch
Why did you prepare so many dishes?
Nothing
I’ll come here often. I’m so happy.
My siblings must be very busy, right?
Soo Gyeom is old enough to get married.
Before that, I have to work hard for him.
- Brother
- Luo Su
- What?
- It's okay. You say it first.
Things about Kukkiwon
You know that's Taizheng Telecom
A customer for more than ten years, right?
know
but i went there
Directly planted the ACT flag
The price negotiated is also very high
Well done
But do you know who Tai Zheng sent at that time?
I can't believe it's actually Xu Tae-hwan
Do you know what he said to me?
He begged me not to sign Kukkiwon
He begged me that if I lost this project
Taizheng Telecom is completely finished.
But I didn't hesitate for a moment
Why?
Because ACT has supported our family for 25 years
I work for the great ACT
Who cares if a former colleague lives or dies?
Or am I fired? What does it have to do with me?
Luo Zhu
I still owe so much to ACT and need to pay it back...
Kim Nak Soo!
The HR team will talk to you tomorrow
- Brother
- Yes
- for...
- Brother
don't do this to me
You know better than anyone that these 25 years
How hard do I work at ACT?
you can't do this to me
To clean up the mess for you
I was not able to attend Soo Gyom’s graduation ceremony even once.
Your son and daughter's graduation ceremony
I didn't leave any one behind. They all went.
But my Soo-gyeom’s graduation ceremony
I haven't been able to go there even once
Brother
Have I ever complained to you?
The trouble you caused is all caused by me.
But I never cared about you
That's all I do for you
Brother
you can't do this to me
Xu Tae-hwan and I are different
I did a good job and I'm still doing a good job
I even got a big order
I'm still useful to the company
You have worked hard these years
What?
Brother
I can work harder
Luo Zhu
How could you do this to me?
What did I do wrong?
Are you going to Banpo-dong?
Yes, it's me
That black car over there
Okay, then I'll start the car
sorry
Damn it
(Facilities Management Team)
Try starting
good
Is the car broken down?
It's indeed broken
It's time to scrap it
Good
Take a photo
(Seoul 32 DA7982)
(to be scrapped)
- good morning
Good
(ACT Login)
(Creative Contest for Improving Work Culture)
music
(Early morning playlist when you don’t want to go to work)
(Sales department structure adjustment)
(Personal personnel transfer order)
(Sales Team Manager Kim Nak-soo)
(Transferred to Asan Factory Safety Management Team Leader)
(Transfer date: May 19, 2025)
"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Safety and Health Management Manager
Why do this?
It’s time to eat!
I have been working at ACT for 25 years 25 years!
What are you doing? I can’t do it anymore
-Are you going to resign?
- Yes!
You said it yourself
We all have to be responsible for our own choices
(17th Real Estate Agent Examination)
- Safety first!
Very good!
Then let’s see how you are responsible
Because of the loss of Kim Nak-soo
And the shaky ACT sales team!
Just stay quiet
Then leave when you want to leave
That's enough
Subtitle translation: Cheng Jiayue